Guide to the Rice University James Addison Baker College Records, 1956-2020 UA 082
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University James A. Baker College Records
1956-2020
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 082
26.25 Linear Feet (45 boxes)
0.57 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_001 (0.57 GB)
0.0137 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_002 (0.0137 GB)
0.72 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_003 (0.72 GB)
0.38 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_004 (0.38 GB)
9.13 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_005 (9.13 GB)
27.4 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_006 (27.4 GB)
1.02 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0082aip_007 (1.02 GB)
Baker College is one of the five original residential colleges at Rice University. These records consist of material related to college business, social activities, publications, and correspondence, as well as photographs, video, and scrapbooks.
Historical Note
Baker College was established as one of the five original residential colleges at Rice in the fall of 1957. It was named in honor of Captain James Addison Baker who served as the Rice Institute's first chairman on the Board of Trustees.
The College went co-ed in the Fall of 1973. Following the opening of the Institute in 1912, the first buildings that comprise the present Baker College were constructed. The first unit to be completed in the residence area of the new institution was the present Commons of Baker, which was to serve as the central dining hall for the entire campus for forty-three years. The next building completed was East Hall, which is now known to members as the "Old Wing" of Baker. These buildings remained unchanged until the installation of the college system at Rice in 1957 when the addition of the "New Wing" and Baker House completed the present Baker College. The Baker House is home of the College Master and his family.
The Charter Members of Baker College, under the leadership of the first cabinet, declared the purpose of their college to be: "to provide and maintain an atmosphere and environment which will encourage the intellectual and social growth of its members through the development of a sense of responsibility in all spheres of community action." Excerpted from "Baker College Hell-O Week Book," 1997
Scope and Contents
The collection includes cabinet meeting minutes, reports such as budget and annual reports, news clippings, correspondence, Baker Books, college publications, programs, photographs, video, and theatrical material as well as other college files on O-Week, freshman week and more.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Accruals
Future additions are expected for this material.
Acquisition Information
The original files were transferred to the Woodson Research Center in the 1970s. On May 2, 1990 Pat Magee added to those records and additional materials arrived in 2010 and 2012. Elena Lacey and Jarrod Boyd donated materials in 2012. In May 2014, Venora Frazier, the longtime College Coordinator, donated all of her files.
Related Material
See the Rice University Archives for records about other Rice University residential colleges. See also Information Files for more about the residential college system or the Baker family. Contact Woodson Research Center staff for assistance.
Bibliography
The history of student life at Rice University: a series of papers; editor, Michael Raphael; project director, Patricia Martin; authors, Colin Delany ... [et al.]. [Houston, Tex.]: Rice [University], c. 1990. A history of Rice University: the Institute years, 1907-1963; Fredericka Meiners; published in cooperation with the Rice University Historical Commission [by] Rice University Studies, 1982.
Index Terms
Subjects
Education; Universities and colleges; Social life and customs
Document Types
clippings (information artifacts); annual reports; corrrespondence; minutes (administrative records); programs (documents); photographs
Subjects (Persons)
Baker, James Addison
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University--residential college system; Baker College (Rice University)
- Series I: Publications and documents, 1956-2009; 36904
  - The Baker Book (handbook), 1964, 1966-1969, 1972-1977, 1979-1980, 1982.; 36949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Baker Associates booklet, 1970, n.d.; 36948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Baker Book (handbook), 1984-1991, 1993-1997; 36947 (Box 1a, Folder 1)
  - Convocation, 1966, 1969, 1973, 1998, 2004; 36946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Resident directories, 1968-1989; 36945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Baker College Documents, 1968, 1971, 1973, 1997, 1978; 36944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vitis, 1960/1961; 36943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vitis, 1961/1962; 36942 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vitis, 1963/1964; 36941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vitis, 1964/1965; 36940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vitis, 1965/1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vitis, 1966/1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vitis, 1967/1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vitis, 1968/1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vitis, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1956-; 36939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committee/Council, 1968-; 36938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Policies, 1968-; 36937 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report of Baker College, 1968-1969; 36936 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1969, 1973-1974, 1978-1982, n.d.; 36935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Budgets, Treasurer's reports, 1969, 1973-75; 36934 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Baker bus, c. 1972; 36933 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fifteenth Anniversary program, April 5, 1972; 36932 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions, 1972, 1975, n.d.; 36931 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Play production programs, news clips, 1973-1982; 36930 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Freshmen week, August 1974; 36929 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires, studies, 1974-1975; 36928 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Orientation week, 1975-1976, 1995, 1998, 2009; 36927 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Community/University/Faculty Associates, 1975-1977; 36926 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Email/memos, 1995-; 36925 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series II: Cabinet meeting minutes, 1968-1991; 110903
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Sept. 1968 - Aug. 1972; 36923 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Sept. 1972 - April 1973; 36922 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Sept. 1973 - April 1974; 36921 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1974 - April 1975; 36920 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1975 - April 1976; 36919 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1976 - April 1977; 36918 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1977 - April 1978; 36917 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1978 - April 1979; 36916 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1979 - April 1980; 36915 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Sept. 1980 - April 1981; 36914 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1981 - April 1982; 36913 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1982 - March 1983; 36912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, April 1983 - April 1984; 36911 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1984 - April 1985; 36910 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1985 - April 1986; 36909 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1986 - Nov. 1987; 36908 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, 1988; 36907 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, 1989-1990; 36906 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, 1991-; 36905 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Series III: College photographs and ephemera, 1956-2003; 110904
  - Student registrations A-K, 1950's-1970's; 110827 (Box 6)
  - Student registrations L-Z, 1950's-1970's; 110828 (Box 7)
  - Photographs and Video, 1996, n.d.; 110829 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Freshmen, Sophomore negatives, 1998; 110830 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Junior slides and negatives, 1998-1999; 110831 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Senior slides and negatives, 1999-2000; 110832 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Summer/Fall negatives, 2000; 110833 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and Coat of Arms, 1956-1958, n.d.; 110834 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sketch of Baker College seal, n.d.; 110837 (Box 9)
  - Embroidered seal, n.d.; 110836 (Box 9)
  - Photograph Second Baker College Cabinet, 1957-1958; 110835 (Box 9)
  - Slides, photographs, and negatives, 1972-1978, 1995, n.d.; 110838 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Baker O-week (orientation), 2000; 110839 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Spring Theatre Festival promotional photographs, n.d.; 110840 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Baker College Associates, 2000-2003; 110841 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1999 roommate questionnaires, 110842 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Reunion, listserve, minutes, 1995-1999, n.d.; 110843 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newcomer's Guide, Constitution, 1996, 1998; 110844 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 1995, n.d.; 110845 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 1996; 110846 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Baker College Flag designs, 1998; 110847 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Student scrapbook photos and news clippings, 1999-2002; 143936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Baker College Associates ephemera, 1998-2004, n.d.; 143937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Articles related to Baker College, 1998; 143938 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Cabinet and Student Association documents, 1983-1985; 143939
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Feb. 1983 - Apr. 1983; 143940 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1983 - Dec. 1983; 143941 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Jan. 1984 - Apr. 1984; 143942 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Aug. 1984 - Dec. 1984; 143943 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Meeting minutes, Jan. 1985 - Mar. 1985; 143944 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Student Association meeting minutes, Jan. 1984 - Feb. 1985; 143945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet and Association members lists and policies, 1983-1985; 143946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Financial and budget papers, 1982-1984; 143947 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1985, n.d.; 143948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Calendars, 1983-1984; 143949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Other houses material, 1983-1985, n.d.; 143950 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Series V: Scrapbooks, 1973-2007; 143951
  - Thresher, 1920; 143953 (Box 12)
  - Unbound student scrapbook, 1973-1976; 143952 (Box 12)
  - Bound student scrapbook, 1957-1963; 184513 (Box 12)
  - Spiral-bound student scrapbook, 2006-2007; 143954 (Box 13)
  - Red student scrapbook with scrollwork, 1982-1988; 143955 (Box 13)
  - Red student scrapbook with gold trim, 1976-1982; 143956 (Box 13)
  - Melissa Sanchez, 2001-2003; 143957 (Box 14)
  - Mimi Zhang, n.d.; 143958 (Box 14)
- Series VI: Governance, 1973-1979; 160182
  - Self-Study, 1973; 160183 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SA Constitution - Baker President's Copy, April 1975; 160184 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Baker College Retreat, 1977-1979; 160185 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Committee Reports, 1977-1979; 160186 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Endowment Fund of Baker College, 1979; 160187 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Security Parking Plan, 1979; 160188 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - External Vice President, 1970s; 160189 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - President's Papers, 1985/1986; 160190 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - President's Papers - Charles Fox (1 of 3), 1981/1982; 160191 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - President's Papers - Charles Fox (2 of 3), 1981/1982; 160192 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - President's Papers - Charles Fox (3 of 3), 1981/1982; 160193 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - President's Papers - Ed Keller (1 of 2), 1982/1983; 160194 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - President's Papers - Ed Keller (2 of 2), 1982/1983; 160195 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - President's Papers - John Knox, 1983/1984; 160196 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Series VII: Masters, RAs, and Associates, 1973-2012; 160197
  - David Minter, 1973-1981; 160198 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Charles Garside, Jr. Tribute, 1987; 160199 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Associates and Awards Night, 1997, 2011-; 160265 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Cabinet Meeting Minutes, 1962-2011; 160200
  - September 1962 - May 1963, 160201 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - September 1963 - February 1964, 160202 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - September 1964 - May 1965, 160203 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - September 1965 - May 1966, 160204 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - September 1966 - May 1967, 160205 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - September 1967 - May 1968, 160206 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - March 22, 1994-April 24, 1996, 161943 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - April 2011, 160266 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Series IX: Newsletters/Newsclippings, 1967-2001; 160207
  - Vitis, 1969/1970; 160208 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Vitis, 1970/1971; 160209 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Vitis, 1971/1972; 160210 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Vitis, 1972/1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Vitis, 1973/1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Vitis, 1974/1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Vitis, 1975/1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Vitis, 1977/1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Cap'n Baker Presents, 1972-1974, 1983; 160211 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1999-, 160212 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Series X: Student Life, 1958-2017; 160213
  - Baker Night, December 1958; 160214 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Baker Night, December 1959; 160215 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Baker Night, December 1960; 160216 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Baker Night, December 1961; 160217 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Baker Night, December 1962; 160218 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Baker Night, December 1963; 160219 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Baker Night, December 1964; 160220 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Baker Night, December 1965; 160221 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Baker Night, December 1966; 160222 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Baker Night, 1967; 160223 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Theater, 1976-78, 1983, 1988, c. 1990, 2000, 2002, 2012; 160224 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Shakespeare Feasting, 1977, 1980; 160225 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Beer Bike, 1999, 2011-2012; 160226 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 80s Neon GlO-Week Book, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - College Night, Spring 2017 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - New Member Blurbs, undated; 160227 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Series XI: Photographs, 1980-2001; 160228
  - Shakespeare Feasting, c. 1980; 160229 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - O-Week - MentOs-Week, 1998; 160235 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Beer Bike, 1999; 160230 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Negatives - Beer Bike, 1999; 160231 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - O-Week - GI Jane and Joe Week (1 of 2), 2001; 160232 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - O-Week - GI Jane and Joe Week (2 of 2), 2001; 160233 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Athletes, undated; 160234 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Series XII: Audio/Visual, 1988-2005; 160236
  - The Phantom Tollbooth (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 15, 1988; 160237 (Box 19, Item 1)
  - Julius Caesar, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 1998; 160238 (Box 19, Item 2)
  - Juius Caesar, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 1998; 160239 (Box 19, Item 3)
  - Midsummer's Night Dream, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 26, 1999; 160240 (Box 19, Item 4)
  - Midsummer's Night Dream, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 26, 1999; 160241 (Box 19, Item 5)
  - Camelot, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 20, 1999; 160242 (Box 19, Item 6)
  - Camelot, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 20, 1999; 160243 (Box 19, Item 7)
  - Baker (8mm Camcorder Tape), 2000; 160244 (Box 19, Item 8)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 23, 2000; 160245 (Box 19, Item 9)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 23, 2000; 160246 (Box 19, Item 10)
  - Macbeth, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), April 7, 2001; 160247 (Box 19, Item 11)
  - Macbeth, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), April 7, 2001; 160248 (Box 19, Item 12)
  - Twelfth Night, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 23, 2002; 160249 (Box 19, Item 13)
  - Twelfth Night, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 23, 2002; 160250 (Box 19, Item 14)
  - Hello Again (8mm Camcorder Tape), undated; 160251 (Box 19, Item 15)
  - Much Ado about Nothing (VHS), 1996; 160252 (Box 19, Item 16)
  - The Winter's Tale (VHS), 1997; 160253 (Box 19, Item 17)
  - Othello (VHS), 2004; 160254 (Box 19, Item 18)
  - The Taming of the Shrew (VHS), March 31, 2005; 160255 (Box 19, Item 19)
  - Drive Thru Edits (VHS), undated; 160256 (Box 19, Item 20)
  - Senior Slide Show/O-Week (VHS), undated; 160257 (Box 19, Item 21)
  - The Taming of the Shrew (1 of 2) (DVD), March 2005; 160258 (Box 19, Item 22)
  - The Taming of the Shrew (2 of 2) (DVD), March 2006; 160259 (Box 19, Item 23)
  - All's Well That Ends Well, 1994 (Box 19, Item 24)
  - Macbeth production and publicity photographs (CD), Spring (Box 19, Item 25)
  - Photographs (CD), 2012; 160267 (Box 19, Item 26)
- Series XIII: Oversized and Scrapbook, 1968-2011; 160261
  - Hamlet poster, 2011; 160274 (Box 20, Item 1)
  - The Tempest poster, 1985; 184510 (Box 20, Item 2)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream poster, 1986; 184511 (Box 20, Item 3)
  - Baker College Associates Award, undated; 160275 (Box 20, Item 4)
  - Holiday Card, undated; 160263 (Box 20, Item 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1968-1973; 160264 (Box 20, Item 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1993/1994; 184512 (Box 20, Item 7)
  - Hello Again poster, 2002 (Box 20, Item 8)
  - Much Ado About Nothing poster (2), 1996 (Box 20, Item 9)
- Series XIV: T-Shirts and Memorabilia, 1968-2012; 160268
  - Baker Bear Team short-sleeved sweatshirt, c. 1969; 160269 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - The Tempest, 1992; 160270 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Toga! Toga! Orientation Week T-Shirt (2), 1994; 160271 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - Sunglasses, undated; 160273 (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Special Service Award for Lynette Bishop with letter, 1998; 160580 (Box 21, Item 5)
  - Special Service Award for Lynette Bishop, 2003; 160581 (Box 21, Item 6)
  - Baker College glass, n.d. (Box 21, Item 7)
  - Bronze wine coaster with Baker insignia, undated; 160582 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Rice University Broomball Champions Trophy, 2006; 162384 (Box 21, Item 9)
  - Texas Braincell Massacre Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 1998; 184507 (Box 21, Item 10)
  - Scooter Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 1999; 184508 (Box 21, Item 11)
  - Buzzed Lightbeer Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 2000; 184506 (Box 21, Item 12)
  - Barley's Angels Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 2001; 184509 (Box 21, Item 13)
  - Baker College Honor Course plaques, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Item 14-16)
  - Mentors/Co-Mentors plaque, 1981 (Box 21, Item 17)
- Series XV: 50th Anniversary of the College System Display, 2007, 162385
  - Important dates and documents, 2007; 162386 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 2007; 162387 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Series XVI: Publications, 1982-2005, 162388
  - The Baker Book, 1982; 162392 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Prohibition Book, 1992; 162393 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Baker Associates, 1995; 1990; 162389 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Baker in Wonderland Book, 1996; 162394 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hell O-Week Book, 1997; 162395 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Mentos Week Book, 1998; 162396 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Constitution of Baker College, August 1998; 162390 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Camelot, November 1999; 162403 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jacques Cousteau Week Book, 2000; 162397 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Top Secret Book, 2001; 162398 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - E-I-E-I-O-Week Book, 2002; 162399 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Pharaoh Week Book, 2005; 162400 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Series XVII: Governance, 1984-2013, 173086
  - Bylaws, 2010; 173089 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws, 2012; 173090 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws, 2013; 173091 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Directory, 1984/1985; 173092 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet Directory, 1985/1986; 173095 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Positions, 2010; 173093 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Changes to Cabinet Positions, 2013; 173094 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Constitution, 2010; 173096 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Constitution, 2013; 173097 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Directory, 1984/1985; 173098 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 2010/2011; 173099 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Series XVIII: O-Week, 1970-2014, 173087
  - O-Week book, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - O-Week documents, 2012; 173100 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - To Camelot We GO-Week Book, 2012; 173101 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Caesar to NerO-Week Book, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Baker Books and O-Week books, 1970-1971, 1978, 1981, 1983, 1999, 2003-2004, 2006-2007; 0.57 Gigabytes
    Scope and Contents
    pdf scans of Baker Books and O-Week books.
- Series XIX: Memorabilia, 2009-2012, 173088
  - 80s Neon GlO-Week T-Shirt, 2009; 173102 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Legends of the Hidden Temple - College Night T-Shirt, Spring 2011; 173103 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Bacardi Rock Anthem - Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 2012; 173104 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Baykah in Jamaica - College Night T-Shirt, Spring 2012; 173105 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - To Camelot We GO-Week T-Shirt, 2012; 173106 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - Baker Comes First T-Shirt, 2012; 173107 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - Divisional Advising stamps (4), n.d.; 184574 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cap'n Crunk - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2010 (Box 24, Item 8)
  - Centennial T-Shirt, 2012 (Box 24, Item 9)
  - Baker 13 T-Shirt, 2011 (Box 24, Item 10)
  - To Camelot We GO-Week Banner, 2012; 173108 (Map-drawer 148, Item 19)
    General Note
    Rice University Architectural drawings, oversize manuscript material, maps and photographs, Part 3 of 3 (UA 226-3)
- Series XX: Administrative Files, 1968-2013, 183378
  - Subseries A: 1960s, 183379
    - College Courses, 1968/1969; 183380 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - College Courses, 1969/1970; 183381 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: 1970s, 183382
    - College Courses, 1970/1971; 183383 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - College Courses, 1971/1972; 183384 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - College Courses, 1972/1972; 183385 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - College Courses, 1973/1974; 183386 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - College Courses, 1974/1975; 183387 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - College Courses, 1975/1976; 183388 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - College Courses, 1976/1977; 183389 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - College Courses, 1977/1978; 183390 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - College Courses, 1978/1979; 183391 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - College Courses, 1979/1980; 183392 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1979/1980; 183394 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Subseries C: 1980s, 183393
    - College Courses, 1980/1981; 183395 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1980/1981; 183396 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Awards/Honors, 1981/1982; 183397 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Cabinet, 1981/1982; 183398 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - College Courses, 1981/1982; 183399 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Commencement, 1981/1982; 183400 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1981/1982; 183401 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Student Lists, 1981/1982; 183402 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Awards/Honors, 1982/1983; 183403 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Cabinet, 1982/1983; 183404 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Commencement, 1982/1983; 183405 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1982/1983; 183406 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Student Lists, 1982/1983; 183407 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Awards/Honors, 1983/1984; 183408 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Cabinet, 1983/1984; 183409 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - College Courses, 1983/1984; 183410 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Commencement, 1983/1984; 183411 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1983/1984; 183412 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Student Lists, 1983/1984; 183413 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Awards/Honors, 1984/1985; 183414 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Cabinet, 1984/1985; 183415 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Commencement, 1984/1985; 183416 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1984/1985; 183417 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Student Lists, 1984/1985; 183418 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - College Courses, 1985/1986; 183419 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1985/1986; 183420 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Student Lists, 1985/1986; 183421 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - College Courses, 1986/1987; 183423 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1986/1987; 183424 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Student Lists, 1986/1987; 183425 (Box 26, Folder 3)